练习 11-2：The Vile VIP。请跟读，注意 V 和 W。
Exercise 11-2, the vile VIP. Repeat after me, focusing on V and W. Of is pronounced
of. When revising his visitor's version of a plan for a very well-paved avenue, the
VIP was advised to reveal none of his motives. Eventually, however, the hapless
visitor discovered his knavish views and confided that it was vital to review the
plans together to avoid a conflict. The VIP was not convinced and averred that he
would have it vetoed by the Vice President. This quite vexed the visitor,
who then vowed to invent an indestructible paving compound in order to avenge his
good name. The VIP found himself, on the verge of a civil war, with a visitor with
whom he had previously conversed easily. It was only due to his inseparable vanity
that the inevitable division arrived as soon as it did. Never again did the
visitor converse with the vain VIP and they remained divided forever.